

Gracie Lundell

Creative Technologist in Portland, OR

(971) 322 - 3400

gracielundell@gmail.com



gracielundell.com

Technical Skills	Frameworks
CSS ₃ /Sass	Ember.js
JavaScript	Vue.js
HTML5	Materialize
Git / Git workflow / Github	Bootstrap

UX/UI Foundation

Design Skills Tools Webflow Wireframing inVision **Prototyping** Sketch **Product Architecture** Agile Methodologies Responsive Design Wrike Project Management

OVERVIEW

I am fascinated with all sides of the product ecosystem. I have experience with both front-end development and wireframing applications which allows me to straddle design and development. The combination of these skills, as well as my knowledge of preprocessing engines allows me to collaborate with others to build useful prototypes quickly and efficently.

PROJECTS

Cafe 26 — Restaurant Website MAY 2017

Pug

I designed and developed a static website using HTML/SCSS/jQuery and media queries to ensure a smooth experience for both mobile and desktop devices using the Materialize components library and guidelines.

Grow — *Gardening App* MAY 2017

Grow is a mobile gardening app to help people keep track of their gardens. This project compares my work and designs from last year to what I have learned while working for a startup where I got a extensive education in designing wireframes, project systems, and prototyping. It is an examination of my UX and design practices and focuses on user interactions.

Scout — *Social Media App* MAY 2016

A social media mobile app designed to help users explore new cities. I worked with a team and lead the design of the user experience, logo, and main interactions for the site.

EXPERIENCE

Fyre Media — Jr. Product Engineer SEPTEMBER 2016 - MAY 2017

As member of the Product Team, I worked closely with other designers and developers on multiple aspects of the booking platform to implement the core feature set.

- Contributed to the component library using Vue.js, Materialize, and Pug
- Wireframe the structure of the key feature of the product using Sketch for mobile and desktop.
- Built and maintained prototypes using Invision.

Black Tower Entertainment — Remote Intern JUNE 2016 - JULY 2016

A five-week internship where I focused on CSS/ Sass and Ember.js for the soon-to-be released web game, Iron Vice:

- Managed and implemented the redesign for the lobby menu page
- · Designed wireframes and lead discussions with the client to understand their vision,
- Built out the decided-upon design using Sass in conjunction with existing components built in the Ember.js framework.

EDUCATION

Epicodus, Portland, Or Front-end Web Design JANUARY 2016 - JULY 2016

A vocational school for junior software developers where I studied JavaScript with a focus on CSS, Web Design, and User Experience for front-end web development. I gained pair-programming skills, and learned how to collaborate and communicate with others.